Opening the hospital appointment system login page.
Filling in the email address for patient login.
Entering the password securely.
Submitting the login form to authenticate.
Login successful. Redirecting to patient dashboard.
Viewing current appointments on the dashboard.
Clicking on Book New Appointment button.
Selecting the medical department from dropdown.
Choosing an available doctor for the appointment.
Picking the appointment date and time.
Submitting the appointment booking form.
Appointment created successfully. Returning to dashboard.
Verifying the new appointment appears in the list.