Opening the hospital appointment system login page.
Filling in the email address for patient login.
Entering the password securely.
Submitting the login form to authenticate.
Login successful. Redirecting to patient dashboard.
Viewing current appointments on the dashboard.
Navigating to Departments section.
Viewing existing departments in the system.
Going to Doctors section.
Clicking Add Doctor button.
Entering doctor name and details.
Selecting department for the doctor.
Entering phone number and contact information.
Creating doctor record in the system.
Doctor added successfully to the database.
Navigating to Patients section.
Clicking Add Patient button.
Entering patient name and personal details.
Setting patient age and date of birth.
Entering phone number for patient contact.
Creating patient record in the system.
Patient registered successfully.
Going to Appointments section.
Clicking Book Appointment button.
Selecting doctor for the appointment.
Selecting patient for the appointment.
Setting appointment date and time.
Entering visit reason and notes.
Booking appointment in the system.
Appointment created successfully.
Returning to Dashboard.
Viewing updated statistics and summary.
Demo complete. Thank you for watching.